Let's start the third party tools or the other armament tools that was used for command
and control.
So, we have already seen the any desk, but we have multiple armament tools in place.
So, this will be also used for command and control, and we have a splash top, this is also
one of the oily used armament tools by the attackers to do something.
And we have a type VNC, this is one of the armament tools that was oily used by the
attackers to do something inside the machine.
Also, we have a theta, this is a remote monitoring and management tool.
So, this is also used by other attackers in multiple incidents.
And we have multiple armament tools, we have the crown remote desktop, so this is also
one of the armament tools that used in multiple incidents.
So, we have set of armament tools, so based on your requirement, you can use the armament
tools which you need for command and control.
I hope you have a clear understanding about this one, let's hope from here we will continue
our discussion in next video series.